Juan Daniel Sánchez

Full Stack Web Developer

CONTACTS











SKILLS

- React JS
- Redux
- Node JS Express JS
- PostgreSQL
- Sequelize
- Sass

LENGUAGES

English B2

Able to speak in basic conversations. Good reading and writing skills.

PROFILE

Full Stack web developer with the ability to learn fast, work and adapt quickly to constantly changing environments. I have experience working with technologies such as Javascript, React, Redux, Node JS, Express JS, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Sass and GitFlow, as well as teamwork, project planning and agile methodologies (SCRUM). In my last project I was in charge of the Front End area, where I was responsible for implementing the user interface and client side logic. Creative, self-motivated, proactive and fully focused on achieving goals.

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Teaching Assistant | HENRY

4 months

Bootcamp Pre Course Assistant (Henry Hero) for Full-Stack Development Students

- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises vía Slack.
- Live lectures to students
- · Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes

2020 - 2021 Personal Projects

Dogs App - Full Stack Web Developer

I built a SPA with React, Redux, Express JS and PostgreSQL where i learned how to integrate a client side with server side, as well as build a simple API REST and make several API calls Demo

Rocket Job App - Front End Developer

I worked in the front end area designing the user interface and creating the logical functionalities from the client side. I learned Route protection, implementation of a login system, flow in github and teamwork. <u>Demo</u>

2015 - 2020 Surgical Technician | IPS Universitaria

I worked assisting all kinds of surgeries, compromising the safety and care of the patient. There I developed skills such as assertive communication, teamwork, resilience. As well as teaching and training students during their internship period.

EDUCATION

HENRY

Full Stack Web Developer

800+ theoretical-practical hours in React, Redux, Express, PostgreSQL and Sequelize 2022

Platzi

React Developer - Responsive Web Design

Universidad de Antioquia Surgical Technician

2011 - 2015